Guide to the Lee Felsenstein Papers M1443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 8: Accession 2017-243
  - Subseries 8.1: Contracting & Consulting Work
    - Job 145 - X86 CPUs (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Job 145 - PPC CPUs (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Job 145 - Strongarm CPUs (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Job 145 - MIPS CPUs (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Job 145 - Receipts (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Job 145 Notes (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Job 146 - US 6,124,708 Pos'n Detection (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Job 146 - 5,815,091 Position Encoder (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Job 146 - Invoices Contract (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Job 146 - Disclosure (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Job 146 - Patent Application (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Job 147 - Receipts (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Job 149 - Zowie Patent (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - AnyLogic (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Red Jade/H-K (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - BCCI (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Ubiquity (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Palm (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Golemics, Inc., Composition Book (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Phoenix Technologies (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Receipts - Office (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Project Receipts (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Receipts - Shop (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Fonly Profit & Loss (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Fonly Receipts - PPG (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - LTT - Oath & Assignment (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Pemstar Contract Docs (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - County Property Tax (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Misc. Fonly Documents (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Receipts - Travel & Lodging (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Office Lease (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - P & L Statements (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - N Davis (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Singing Fish (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Bricken - FAQ (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Visopia (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - BCCI Development Schedule (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Talima - Stepper Controller (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Talima - Behavioral Specs (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Talima - Rev. A Documents (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Piston Extruder Document CD-Rs (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Talima Piston Extruder Documents (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - 2006 Fonly Invoices (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Mark Goldes MPI (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Tesla Documents - Mobile Charger (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Tesla Rev 4 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Talima Contract (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Talima - Invoices (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Talima Schematics (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - MPI Proposal - Editing (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - LTT Termination Agreement (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Expenses - Receipts and Invoices (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Subs - Mindtribe (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Subs - Voler/McClay (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Ted Smith Talima Invoice (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Misc. Schematics and Notes (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - "Fonly - Biz. Dev." (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Outsell (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Pemstar Employee Listing (Box 50, Folder 32)
      This record contains personal employee information that has been redacted.
    - Osborne 1 User Reference Guide (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Misc. Sequitur Documents (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Interval Research Corp. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 8.2: Jhai PC
    This subseries contains designs, schematics, research, correspondence, and documentation related to the Jhai Foundation’s ‘Remote IT Village Project’, a foot crank-powered computer system designed for rural use in Laos.
    - Info Dev (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Fair Trade Tech (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Jhai PC Publicity/Tech Awards (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Jhai Receipts/Invoices (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Jhai Purchasing (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Jhai Invoice Copies - By Item (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - 150011 Jhai PC Power Switching (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - 051 4104991 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Fair Trade Technologies (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Jhai (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Jhai - List of Drawings, Bills of Materials (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Jhai PC Enclosure 150021 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - JPC Assy. 150004 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - JPC Chassis Assy. 150005 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Jhai - Alarm (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Jhai Printer (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Jhai (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - 150024 - Relay PC Schematic (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - JPC 150001 System, Village (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Jhai - Siting & Installation (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - JPC Switch Box Assembly 150016 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Jhai - Power Budgeting (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Jhai Presentations (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Jhai - Wireless (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Jhai PC Monitor (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - MZ104 + Manual (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Jhai PC Village System (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - JPC - Power Generation (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - JPC - Hesc Power Reg./Charger (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Jhai - Pedal Generator (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Jhai - Proj. Planning (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Jhai - Antennas (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - TM Crusoe (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Jhai PC Documents (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Misc. Jhai Documents (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Misc. Jhai Documents (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 8.3: Parts Orders and Documentation
    This subseries contains order forms, specifications, technical documentation, and user manuals related to electronics parts. It also features press releases and publicity related to technologies of interest.
    - Java - Personal Apple Envelope (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - MOT MPC823E (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Interwave Documents (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Digi-Key (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Orcad/Cadence (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - VPC (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - AVR Atmel Dev Sys (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - PPG Tech (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Sony ICD B15 Digital Voice Recorder (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - FedEx (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Polcraft (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Magnetoelastic Power Generators (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - PPG Spec Sheets (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Rotomag - Fonly (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - MZ104 - EV Manual (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Plexus (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Cipher Tape Drive (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Parts Order Form, 05-11-1986 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - GE Press Release (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - "The Guitarist's Fake-Card" Design Documents (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Misc. Manuals and Specifications (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Misc. Invoices & Financial Reports (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Misc. Email Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Parts Catalogs, Manuals, and Publicity (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries 8.4: Personal Schematics and Notes
    This subseries comprises various schematics, designs, and notes related to various personal and professional projects.
    - Ideo (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Office Layout (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Dervish Char Set (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - NEC NL10276AC24-05 LCD Data Sheet (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Kid's Pals (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - PPG History & Design Notes (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - PPG Marketing & Specs (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Fonly - Generator Test Stand (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Hold-Up Circuit (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - IQ Increase (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Personal Documents (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Documents and Notes (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Personal Schematics, Notes, and Code (Box 52, Folder 3-4)
  - Subseries 8.5: Nonprofit Documents & Communications
    This subseries comprises materials related to pro bono work, conferences, and extra-professional endeavors and related communications.
    - The Free Speech Movement Archives (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Free Speech Movement Mailing List (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - OLPC (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - OLPC (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Hackers & Asilomar Lists (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - AMW Rosters / PGMs (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Fonly Institute Prospectus (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Information Guide on Presort First-Class Mail (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Misc. Correspondence and Memos (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 8.6: Computer Media (CLOSED)
    Two cartons of computer media (not numbered) are closed until processed.